(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-01T00:04:32.821836",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
路地裏の真ん中で 慣れない景色と
In the middle of a back alley, with unfamiliar scenery
好きじゃない匂いに 私は覆われて 染まっていくんでしょう
and a scent I don't like covering me, I guess I'm being tainted.
私は怖がりで 知らないことには手を出さず 誰かがやってきて 毒味をするまで待っていた
I'm a coward who wouldn't touch anything unfamiliar, waiting until someone came along to test for poison.
することは単純で マニュアル通りの生活を 来る日も淡々と過ごしていた
What I had to do was simple: living a manual-like life, spending day after day indifferently.
そういやさ そういやさ 昨日の私もこうだった そういやさ そういやさ
Come to think of it, come to think of it, yesterday's me was just like this. Come to think of it, come to think of it,
弱い音を吐いてる 薄っぺらい人間です
I'm a shallow person who spits out weak complaints.
一歩前に出るのはやめておきます 絡まれたくはないからさ
I'll refrain from stepping forward, because I don't want to get involved.
描いた理想像に現実味がないから 近づけないよう生きておきます 明日も同じよう過ごしておきます
Since my ideal image lacks reality, I'll live keeping my distance, and pass tomorrow the same way.
路地裏の真ん中で いつもの夕日を薄目で眺めて 胸の内で呟いた 「いつまで続くだろう」
In the middle of a back alley, squinting at the usual sunset, I whispered in my heart, "How long will this go on?"
そういやさ そういやさ 昨日も夕飯これだった そういやさ そういやさ
Come to think of it, come to think of it, yesterday's dinner was this too. Come to think of it, come to think of it,
臆病で切りが悪い 意気地無し人間です
I'm a timid, indecisive, cowardly human being.
一歩後ろに下がって逃げておきます 目立ちたくなんかはないからさ
I'll step back and run away, because I don't want to stand out.
描いた理想像に現実味がないから 近づけないよう生きておきます 明日も同じよう過ごしておきます
Since my ideal image lacks reality, I'll live keeping my distance, and pass tomorrow the same way.
弱い音を吐いてる 薄っぺらい人間です 一歩前に出るのはやめておきます 絡まれたくはないからさ
I'm a shallow person who spits out weak complaints. I'll refrain from stepping forward, because I don't want to get involved.
ため息ばっかでさ 吸う息足りないの きっとそう上手くはいかないけどさ 試しにちゃんと生きてみよう
I'm always sighing, not getting enough breath. It probably won't go so well, but as a test, let's try to live properly.
鉄の弾が 正義の証明 貫けば 英雄に近づいた
An iron bullet is proof of justice. Whenever it pierces, I become closer to a hero.
その目を閉じて
Close your eyes...
同じ形
...the same shape...
同じ体温の悪魔
a demon with the same body temperature.
僕はダメであいつがいいの？
Am I no good, but he's alright?
そこに壁があっただけなのに
There was just a wall there, and yet...
生まれてしまった 運命嘆くな
Don't lament the fate of being born.
僕らはみんな 自由なんだから
Because all of us are free.
鳥のように 羽があれば
If I had wings like a bird,
どこへだって 行けるけど
I could go anywhere, but...
帰る場所が なければ
if I have no place to return to,
きっとどこへも 行けない
I surely can't go anywhere.
ただただ生きるの は嫌だ
I just hate living like this.
世界は残酷だ
The world is cruel,
それでも君を愛すよ
but even so, I will love you.
なにを犠牲にしても
No matter what I sacrifice,
それでも君を守るよ
even so, I will protect you.
間違いだとしても 疑ったりしない
Even if it's wrong, I won't doubt it.
正しさとは 自分のこと 強く信じることだ
Righteousness means strongly believing in yourself.
鉄の雨が 降り散る情景 テレビの中 映画に見えたんだ
The scene of falling iron rain looked like a movie on TV.
戦争なんて 愚かな凶暴 関係ない 知らない国の話
War is foolish violence, an story of an unrelated, unknown country.
それならなんで あいつ憎んで 黒い気持ち 隠しきれない理由
Then why do I hate them? The reason I can't hide these dark feelings,
説明だって できやしないんだ 僕らはなんて 矛盾ばっかなんだ
I can't even explain it. How full of contradictions we are!
この言葉も 訳されれば 本当の意味は 伝わらない
If these words are translated, their true meaning won't be understood.
信じるのは その目を開いて 触れた世界だけ
What I believe in is only the world I touch with my eyes open.
ただただ生きるの は嫌だ
I just hate living like this.
世界は残酷だ
The world is cruel,
それでも君を愛すよ
but even so, I will love you.
なにを犠牲にしても
No matter what I sacrifice,
それでも君を守るよ
even so, I will protect you.
選んだ人の影 捨てたものの屍
The shadow of the chosen, the corpses of what was discarded,
気づいたんだ 自分の中 育つのは悪魔の子
I realized that what grows inside me is a child of the devil.
正義の裏 犠牲の中 心には悪魔の子
Behind justice, amidst sacrifice, in my heart is a child of the devil.
そっと振り返った軌跡 どうしたって光って
The path I gently looked back on shines no matter what.
ありふれた君が いつだってスーパーヒーロー
An ordinary you was always a superhero.
いつもポンコツだった私 飛べなくて未完成
I was always clumsy, unable to fly, incomplete.
アヒルの子はアヒルのままかもね なんてさ
"Maybe the duckling stays a duckling," or so I said.
らしさなんてほっといて 君となんかちょっと似ていて
Leaving "being oneself" aside, I'm somewhat like you.
デコボコだからジャストに 噛み合うパズルピース
Because we're uneven, we fit together perfectly like puzzle pieces.
繋ぎたい 繋ぎたい 届かない言葉も
I want to connect, I want to connect, even the words that don't reach.
いつかは誰かの何かになりたいから
Because someday I want to become something to someone.
Crazy no lazy 夢の中 夢を見せて
Crazy, no lazy, show me a dream within a dream.
Always going 何千回 何万回 膝をついても
Always going, no matter how many thousands or tens of thousands of times I drop to my knees,
最大級 i love you で立ち上がれるから
I can stand back up with the ultimate "I love you".
とびっきりオーバーな ty
An extraordinarily over-the-top Thank You.
消えそうなハッピーも 勇気も
The fading happiness and courage...
無理しまっちゃって 大失敗も
Overexerting myself and failing big time,
後悔すら愛せるなら
if I can learn to love even my regrets,
背中には君という羽
then on my back are wings called "you."
チクタク追いこして 積もった乾いた寂しさ
Overtaking tick-tock, dry loneliness accumulated,
隣で走る君と Release, release
running beside you, release, release,
レリーズしたり
release it all...
君の色が 私を塗り替えて
Your color repaints who I am,
壊れかけの 音で響くから
echoing with a broken sound...
おとぎ話の 続きをまだ描きたいんだよ
I still want to paint the continuation of this fairy tale.
パレット パレット 連れて行くよ
Palette, palette, I'll take you along!
きっと難解 案外 難解
Surely complex, unexpectedly complex, complex...
Always going
難解 案外 難解 迷い込んでも
Complex, unexpectedly complex, complex, even if we lose our way,
最大級 I love you な君がいるから
because I have you, whom I love to the maximum degree,
本気 Specialな Thank you
a truly special "Thank you."
それでもってラッキーも 運命も引き寄せて
And with that, pulling in good luck and destiny,
もうバイバイも 涙も忘れないよ
I won't forget goodbyes or tears anymore.
飛べなかった わたしの
For me, who couldn't fly...
この背中には 君という羽
on this back are wings called "you."
Woah... Woah...
描いた未来の 景色がここにある
The scenery of the future I envisioned is right here.
弱さも抱きしめて行くんだから
Because I'll move forward, embracing even my weaknesses...
広げた翼が 輝いていく
The spread wings begin to shine,
飛び立って 明日へ
taking flight into tomorrow!
等身大の私を映してたい
I want to reflect my true, authentic self.
ただ 望む瞬間 衝動になってんだ
Just that desired moment is turning into an impulse.
くだらないとさ 煙り切っていく
Cutting through the smoke of trivial things,
目をそらして 可能性だって夢を見てみたいのに
turning my eyes away, even though I want to dream of possibilities...
ずっとわかっていたんだけど 言葉は浮いてる対象に
I knew it all along, but words float toward their target,
大げささって思ってるんでしょ
thinking it's an exaggeration, right?
ずっと黙っていたんだけど 心ってやっぱ正直だ
I stayed silent all this time, but the heart is honest after all.
閉じ込められたい場所 感じていたい
I want to feel the place where I want to be locked in.
居場所
The place I belong...
響かせて 掲げたカラーで 焦がしてよ 赤色になっていく
Let it resonate, with the colors held high, burn it up, turning into red...
何度も 盗まれたって 取り返した意思の傷跡に
No matter how many times it's stolen, upon the scars of intent reclaimed,
誓った
I swore...
失敗 後悔は泣いて ため息の音がしてる
Failure and regret cry, making the sound of sighs.
現状にそぐわない 飲み込んだ 言ってたんだ
Not matching reality, I swallowed it down, I kept saying...
ああ 忘れないように
Ah, so I don't forget...
降臨祭 もう汚されないように
Advent, so that it won't be stained anymore...
もっと笑っていたいんだもの 大人になってくだいしょうに
Because I want to smile more, as a price for growing up...
あなただってきっと思ってるんでしょ
You surely think so too, right?
ちゃんとわかっていたんだけど 心ってやっぱ正直だ
I understood it well, but the heart is honest after all.
失えなくなった痛みを 感じていたい
I want to feel the pain that I can no longer lose...
暮らしたこの場所で 咲かせた手裏剣 焦がさないでよ
In this place where I lived, the blooming shuriken, don't scorch it,
このまま話は終わっていく
is the story going to end just like this?
何度も
Again and again...
取り戻した日々の傷痕に
On the scars of the days I reclaimed,
誓った
I swore...
ここだよ 響かせて
Right here, make it resound!
心を響かせて
Make my heart resound...
ずっと
Forever...
ここだよ 響かせて
Right here, make it resound!
掲げたこの腕
With this arm raised high,
描いた未来で 賑やかになっていく
in the future I envisioned, it becomes vibrant.
何度でも
Time and time again,
盗まれて手放した 必死の傷痕に
on the frantic scars of what was stolen and released,
誓った
I swore.
はい！
Alright!
皆さん！ということで、本日は常闇トワ生誕祭2025にお越しくださりありがとうございます！
Everyone! Thank you so much for coming to the Tokoyami Towa Birthday Celebration 2025 today!
常闇トワ様です！イエーイ！
It's Tokoyami Towa-sama! Yay!
ちょっと水飲んでもいいですか？水もらっていいですか？すみません。
Can I drink some water? May I get some water? Sorry about that.
ちょっと、すみませんね、水… あ、どこに行ってもカメラが映るのよね。
Sorry about this... Ah, no matter where I go, the camera follows me.
水おいしい！
Water is delicious!
ということで皆さん！今日はライブにお越しいただきありがとうございます！
So, everyone! Thank you so much for coming to the live concert today!
3Dライブをやらせていただいております！ということで、
I'm performing a 3D live concert! And so,
あ、早速なんですけれども、ありがとうみんな！おめでとう！ありがとう！
ah, moving right along... Thank you everyone! Happy Birthday! Thank you!
見えてますよー！
I can see you guys!
はい、早速なんですけれどもね、今回の配信のハッシュタグはこちら！
Alright, moving on, here is the hashtag for today's stream!
#常闇トワ生誕祭2025 ということでね、こちらね、Xでたくさんポストしていただければなと思います！
It's #TokoyamiTowaBirthday2025, so please post a lot on X using this hashtag!
スクリーンショットとかね、感想もいっぱいいただけたら嬉しいです。
I'd be really happy if you shared plenty of screenshots and your thoughts.
スクショはね、もし素敵なのがあったら、ちょっとパクるというか拝借というか… 何て言うんですかね…
As for screenshots, if there are nice ones, I might borrow... or swipe them... whatever you call it...
勝手に「これ使っちゃおう」みたいな感じで使って、後々ポストするかもしれないんですけど、そのために取っといてくれたらなと…
I might casually use them like "I'll use this!" and post them later, so I'd appreciate it if you saved good ones for that...
手伝ってくれたらなと思います！よろしくお願いします！
I'd love it if you could help out! Thank you very much!
フレームワークの共有ね！言い方ね！フレームワークの共有だから！
It's "sharing frameworks"! That's the wording! "Sharing frameworks"!
はい！そして本日はライブだけじゃなくて、色んな発表もしていきたいと思いますので、最後まで見ていてくれれば嬉しいです！
Yes! And today, besides the live performance, I also have various announcements to make, so I'd be happy if you stay tuned until the end!
ここまでなんですけれども、1曲目に和ぬかさんの楽曲の『酔いに愛す』、2曲目に…
Up until now, for the 1st song, it was Wannaka-san's song "Yoi ni Aisu", for the 2nd song...
ヒグチアイさんの『悪魔の子』、そしてトワのオリジナル曲の『S.T.Y.』と『Present Day』を歌わせていただきました！
Higuchi Ai-san's "Akuma no Ko", and then Towa's original songs "S.T.Y." and "Present Day".
今日の配信のオープニングは『Present Day』のインストを使ってます。テンション上がるよね！
Today's stream opening used the instrumental of "Present Day". It really pumps you up, right?
はい、この曲かっこいい！かっこいいけど入りが難しいんで、いつも皆さんに聞こえないところでクリック音をつけてもらってます！
Yeah, this song is so cool! It's cool, but the count-in entry is tough, so I always have a click track playing where you guys can't hear it!
恥ずかしいんですけども、すごい難しいから！はい！
It's embarrassing, but it really is so hard! Yes!
そしてね、今日はちょっと情報がもりもりなんだけど、歌も皆さんに届けしたいと思うので、一回ここでちょっと落ち着いて…
And today is packed full of announcements, but I also want to deliver plenty of songs to you all, so let me take a moment to settle down...
次の曲に行きたいと思います！いっぱい発表がしたいと思うので、本当に待っていてください！
Let's move on to the next song! I have lots of announcements to make, so please stay tuned!
はい！ということで次の曲、オリジナル楽曲続きになります。聴いてください、『My Abyss』。
Alright! So for the next song, it's another original song. Please listen: "My Abyss".
堕 堕 堕 沈んでいく ダーダ dirty value
Fall, fall, fall, sinking down... Dada dirty value
怒 怒 怒 忘れて 混じり合う who am I?
Rage, rage, rage, forgetting and blending together, who am I?
目 目 目 這い寄るこの気持ちは もう溶けて消えていく
Eyes, eyes, eyes... This creeping feeling is already melting away and vanishing.
絡まった導火線には 火花近づけ play on
Bring a spark close to the tangled fuse, play on.
輪廻には
Left behind by reincarnation...
逃げ遅れて
I failed to escape...
あなたはどうして
Why are you...
I wanna be a dancer
今宵溶け合うほどの Dimension
Tonight, a dimension where we melt together
願うのは誰
Who is the one making a wish?
深い闇へ落ちていく
Falling into the deep darkness...
手延ばせ あなたまで
Reach out my hand to you...
届きますように
May it reach you
光刺す先まで
To where the light shines
あなたの手を捕らえますように
May I grasp your hand
I will 光刺す先には
I will... where the light shines
どこまでも広がる Deep Abyss
A deep abyss spreading endlessly
彷徨っていた In the back room
Wandering in the back room
何処でも欲しいんだ Moon
Wanting the moon anywhere
止まらぬ Greed も Free だ
Unstoppable greed is also free
全部手に入れろ Everyone's
Grasp everything, everyone's...
Hey, this is underground
悪辣な夜
A villainous night
我慢しなくてもいいんじゃない
Isn't it fine not to hold back?
もう こっちにおいで
Come over here already
唾棄すべき傷を
Detestable wounds...
手に握ったら Make you evil
If you hold them, make you evil
応えて 誰に触れた？
Answer me, who did you touch?
輪廻には
Left behind...
逃げ遅れて
By reincarnation...
あなたはどうして
Why are you...
I wanna be my master
今宵全て忘れて Welcome to my parade
Forget everything tonight, welcome to my parade
堕ち沈んでいく
Sinking down...
Dirty value
忘れて
Forget it
混ざり合う Who am I?
Blending together, who am I?
低空飛行
Low-altitude flight
この気持ちはもう
This feeling already...
Loop, loop, loop
絡まって解せないわ
Entangled and incomprehensible
言わない近付けないわ
I won't say it, I can't get close
狂ってた 輪廻には
Mad reincarnation...
逃げ遅れて
Left behind...
あなたはどうして
Why are you...
I wanna be a slave
今宵溶け合うほどの Dimension
Tonight, a dimension where we melt together
願うのは誰
Who is the one making a wish?
深い闇へ落ちていく
Falling into the deep darkness...
駆け出して この闇から
Run out, away from this darkness
逃げ出せるように Climb in
So I can escape, climb in
光刺す先まで あなたの手を掴めたら
To where the light shines, if I can grab your hand
I will 光刺す先には
I will... where the light shines
どこまでも広がる Deep Abyss
A deep abyss spreading endlessly
どこまでも深くて
Infinitely deep...
どこまでも続いている Deep Abyss
A deep abyss continuing endlessly
落ちていく
Falling down...
昔々悪魔の娘が 門のない国作ったとさ
Long ago, a devil's daughter created a gate-less kingdom.
やがて多くの人々が集い 賑わった
Soon, many people gathered and it bustled with life.
娘は痛く喜び 迎え入れたが
The daughter was overjoyed and welcomed them, but...
顔のない人々は
The faceless people...
自ら神を名乗り始めた
Started calling themselves gods.
Oh-oh Talk to Talk to デヴォーション Talk to Talk
Oh-oh Talk to Talk to devotion Talk to Talk
顔のない神様の言う通り 供物は毎度子供たち
Just as the faceless gods demanded, the offerings were children each time
の邪気を「あれが欲しい」「これが欲しい」
Their malice, "I want that," "I want this,"
あおられてはただ捏ねる
Stirred up, they just knead it into shape
バズビバザヴ 争いを咲かせとこう
Buzz Be Buzzab, let conflict bloom
瞬く間に 悪魔に 悪魔に みるみる 悪魔に
In the blink of an eye, into devils, into devils, right before your eyes, into devils
瞬く間に 悪魔に 悪魔に あくまで悪魔に
In the blink of an eye, into devils, into devils, devils to the very end
されど連中 なぜ引き裂き 奇跡を乞う
Yet why do those folks tear things apart and beg for miracles?
あれ バズビ バズビ Over
Hey, Buzz Be, Buzz Be, Over
滑稽にクラクラするわ 苛立つわ
It's so ridiculous it makes me dizzy, it's irritating
だから踏んづけちゃお から蹴散らしちゃおう
So let's trample them down and scatter them away!
本気で歌い踊る 夜たり夜たり
Singing and dancing in earnest, night after night
えー？
Eh?
読めてない 混ざってない
Can't read the room, not mixing in
声あわせ唱えましょう
Let us chant together in unison
バズビバザヴ
Buzz Be Buzzab
Save us, God, it's dance time!
どうしたの？
What's wrong?
深くファナティック
Deeply fanatic
浸すロマンティック
Steeping in romanticism
「べきだ」とか ノーサンキューです
Saying "you should" is a "no thank you" from me.
個人的な感想とか
Personal opinions,
悪魔的な妄想とか
Diabolical delusions,
マジ終わってんんだけどさ
Honestly, they're completely ruined.
ウィッシュナ！
Wishna!
ちょっと待って
Wait a second...
瞬く間に
In the blink of an eye,
あっという間に
in an instant,
悪魔に
into a devil,
見る見る悪魔に
right before your eyes into a devil.
瞬く間に あっという間に
In the blink of an eye, in an instant,
悪魔に あくまで悪魔に
into a devil, a devil through and through.
Guilty
Duty
Stupid
Majesty
バズビバザヴ
Bazvibasavu
Order!
牙が出ちゃう グレー クレイジー
Fangs poking out, gray crazy,
セール通り 正しい神話は brand-new
As advertised, the true myth is brand-new.
蛇眼なら ここが聖地
If you have snake eyes, this is the holy ground.
高が目出度い
Celebrating over something so trivial,
フオットにし集え集え
gather around like a whirlwind.
相図は six-six-six
The sign is six-six-six.
宜しくを
Pay your regards,
お辞儀を
bow down,
巻いてインジナイン
and roll with Engine 9.
昔々白馬の娘が 顔の無いマイクで作ったとさ
Once upon a time, a white horse maiden created a faceless mic...
やがて多くの人々が群がり賑わった
Soon, crowds gathered and made it thrive.
真実の歌は踊る
The song of truth dances,
ゆたりゆたり
gently and gracefully.
これってヤバくない？
Isn't this crazy?
怖くない？
Isn't it scary?
声合わせ唱えましょう
Let us sing together in unison,
バズビバザヴ！
Bazvibasavu!
響き出そう
Let it resound!
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute...
元出張り悪魔に悪魔に
From the start, into a devil, a devil,
見る見る悪魔に
right before your eyes into a devil.
元出張り悪魔に悪魔に
From the start, into a devil, a devil,
あくまで悪魔に
a devil through and through.
Guilty
Duty
Stupid
Majesty
バズビバザヴ
Bazvibasavu
Order!
聖母 calling dance time
Holy Mother calling dance time!
心の奥で、残響がする。
Deep within my heart, a reverberation echoes.
それは、
Is that...
過去を超えるための進化か。
An evolution to surpass the past?
魂の奥底へ潜る深化か。
A deepening that dives into the core of the soul?
己の存在を証明する真価か。
Or the true worth proving one's existence?
揺らぎ、信じ、見つけ出した心の芯。
Wavering, believing, and finding the core of the heart.
常闇を裂き、偽りのノイズを消し去って、
Tearing through eternal darkness, erasing false noise,
いま、真実の歌声を
now, unleashing the singing voice of truth...
2ndアルバム 発売決定
2nd Album Release Confirmed!
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Album "SHIN"
参加アーティスト
Participating Artists
響き渡る、始まりの『SHIN』
Resonating, the "SHIN" of beginnings.
はい！
Yes!
ということで、みなさん！
So, everyone!
常闇トワ 2ndアルバム『SHIN』の発表が...
Tokoyami Towa's 2nd album "SHIN" announcement...
発表じゃないわ、発売が決定しましたー！
Not announcement—the release date has been confirmed!
はい！ありがとうございます！お待たせしました！
Yes! Thank you so much! Sorry to keep you waiting!
はい、今回のジャケット写真は、花邑まいさんに描き下ろしていただきました！
So, for this album's jacket illustration, Mai Hanamura drew it for us!
めちゃかっこいいでしょ、これ！
Isn't this super cool?
鎖引きちぎってね、破衣装なんだって！放ちよ！
She's snapping chains, and it's a ripped outfit! Unleashed!
はい！そしてね、10月8日！トワの日ですね！指定させていただきました！
Yes! And it drops on October 8th! Towa's Day! I specifically requested it!
10月8日から、今回もファーストに続き全国流通での発売となっております！
Starting October 8th, just like the first album, it will be available nationwide!
はい、ありがとうございます！
Yes, thank you so much!
豪華作家陣の皆様に書き下ろしていただいた新曲がたくさん収録されております！
It's packed with new songs written by an amazing lineup of creators!
ジャケットいいでしょー！もっと言って！すごい素敵なジャケット描いてくれました！
The cover art is great, right? Tell me more! She drew such a wonderful cover!
そして、2ndアルバムは完全生産限定盤と通常盤の2種類をご用意しております！
And for this 2nd album, we have two editions: Complete Limited Edition and Regular Edition!
まず、完全生産限定盤はこちら！
First, here is the Complete Production Limited Edition!
じゃーん！あ、こっちだった！
Tada! Ah, it was on this side!
外箱が超豪華スリーブボックスになっております！
The outer box comes as a super luxurious slipcase box!
へい！へいだって...はい！「かなた書いて」...へい！
Hey! Why "hey"... Yes! "Kanata wrote that"... Hey!
そして、中身はこちら！
And here are the contents inside!
アクリルブロックキーホルダーやアナザージャケットカード、抽選応募券！
Acrylic block keychain, alternate jacket card, and a lottery entry ticket!
6種類のMVカットステッカーセット、hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME PRカード「常闇トワ」など、豪華特典が盛りだくさん！
6 MV scene sticker sets, hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME PR card "Tokoyami Towa", and tons of bonuses!
ボックスは通常のCDより一回り二回り大きくて、限定盤らしく飾って楽しめるプレミアム仕様です！
The box is 1 to 2 sizes larger than a standard CD, a premium limited edition designed for display!
ボックスの、えー、限定盤となっております。
It comes as a limited box edition.
はい、そしてね、アナザージャケットカードにはランダムでトワのね、直筆サインが入っております！
Yes, and random copies of the alternate jacket cards will feature my handwritten signature!
はい。えー、そしてね、プレゼントキャンペーン賞品のラインナップはこちらです！
Yes. And here is the lineup for the giveaway campaign prizes!
ボーン！
Bam!
はい！このね、キービジュアル...キービジュアルって言うの？これ違うか。ライブのジャケ写？ジャケ写？ジャケ写真？を使った...
Yes! Using the jacket cover photo... or key visual? No, wait, the live album jacket photo?
Tシャツとかポスターとか缶バッジがね...
...T-shirts, posters, and button badges...
出来てます。かっこいいでしょ？
...have been created. Cool, right?
はい。かっこいいの欲しいよね。
Yeah. You want something cool, right?
トワも、トワも欲しい。ごめんけど。
I want one too. Sorry, but I do!
だからトワがじゃあ1枚取るから、2名様と9名様と...
So if I take one, then it'll be for 2 people, 9 people...
嘘ですよ！嘘、嘘！皆さん、皆さんのためにちゃんとありますから！
Just kidding! Just kidding! Don't worry, there's enough for all of you!
はい、そしてね、続いて通常盤はこちらです！
Yes, and moving on, here is the standard edition!
はい、顔のね、ちょっとアップがボーンって入ったような。
Yes! It has a close-up of my face right there.
かっこいい、もう目、もう釘付けでしょ、トワの顔に。
It's so cool. Your eyes are totally glued to my face, right?
はい、えー、こちらのね、デザインとなっておりまして、通常盤にはスマホサイズのジャケットイラストステッカーが入っております。
Yes, this is the design, and the standard edition includes a phone-sized jacket illustration sticker.
こちらのね、かっこいいジャケ写の、えー、ステッカー、スマホに貼ったりPCに貼ったり、
You can stick this cool jacket sticker on your phone, PC,
えー、何ですか？レバーレストとかに貼ったりとか、ね？アゲコに貼ったりとかしてもらえれば嬉しいです！と。
wrist rest, arcade stick, or wherever else you like, and I'd be super happy!
はい！そしてね、えー、こちら！今回のアルバムに楽曲を書き下ろしてくださった作家陣の皆様はこちらです！
Yes! And next, here are all the wonderful songwriters who wrote tracks for this album!
ボーン！
Bam!
実はね、さっき、えー、和ぬかさんの「弱ねはき」だとか、えー、ヒグチアイさんの「悪魔の子」だとか歌ってるけど、なんと！書いてくれてるんですよ！書き下ろしてもらいました！
Actually, earlier I sang Wanuka's "Yowanehaki" and Ai Higuchi's "Akuma no Ko", and guess what? They wrote songs for me! They specially created songs for this album!
実は伏線だったっていうね！
It was actually foreshadowing all along!
はい、ちょっとそういう感じでちょっと組ませていただきました。イエーイ！
Yeah, I planned it that way! Yay!
はい、そうなんですよ。あとね、まあ色々、まあ見てびっくりすることもあると思うんですけども。
Yes, that's right! Also, there might be some surprises when you look at it.
あ、この前の「My Abyss」が収録されてたりとか「Buzzy Buzzy」があったりとかしておりますと。
Oh, "My Abyss" from before is included, as well as "Buzzy Buzzy"!
はい、えー、どの楽曲もすごい素敵に仕上がり、なんでね！楽しみにしていてもらえればと思います！
Yes, every single song turned out so wonderful, so please look forward to it!
はい、そして各店舗別の特典はこちら！ボーン！
Yes, and here are the store-exclusive bonus items! Bam!
もう色んな種類がいっぱいあるからね！もうどの特典も欲しくなると思うんですけども、
There are so many different types! I bet you'll want all of these bonuses,
全部買ってもよし！選んで買ってもよし！ということで、
but buying all of them or picking your favorite is totally fine!
えー、1つ1つ紹介したいところ、えー、これを全部紹介するとたぶん5年ぐらい経つんでね、自分で見てくださいと。
I'd love to introduce them one by one, but if I did that, it would take about 5 years, so please check them out yourself!
えー、完全生産限定盤も通常盤も、えー、絶対手に入れてくださいと。
Be sure to get both the limited edition and the standard edition!
そしてこちらはね、本日21時から発売開始なんですが...
And these will go on sale starting tonight at 9 PM, but...
が！が！が！ホロライブ公式ECでは、なんとこの配信中...
But! But! But! On the official Hololive online store, during this stream...
え、なんですが！が！が！なんとホロライブ公式ECでは...編集点。えー、この配信中にCDが買えるようになるかも！
What, wait... But! But! But! On the official Hololive online store... (edit point!) During this stream, you might actually be able to buy the CD!
なんか出てきてポチって押せたりする...？カカカカ...もう！ということで楽しみに待っていてください！
Something might pop up so you can click it...? Kakaka... Geez! So please wait and stay tuned!
はい！はい！
Yes! Yes!
えー、この後ですね、そして、えー、次の曲はなんとこの後からね、この後、えー、セカンドアルバムから1曲、新曲を披露します！
And after this, for the next song, I'll be performing a brand-new track from my second album!
えー、なるせさん、えー、GTAとかでね、お世話になっているなるせ兄貴ね、お兄ちゃんね、書き下ろしていただきました「chewy chewy」という楽曲になります！
Nqrse-san, big bro Nqrse who has taken care of me in GTA, wrote a new song for me called "chewy chewy"!
はい、この新曲「chewy chewy」はですね、この配信の後にMVが8時50分からプレミア公開！24時に先行リリース予定です！
Yes, for this new song "chewy chewy", the music video will premiere at 8:50 PM right after this stream! And advance release is set for midnight!
やっぱね、なるせさんと言ったらね、言ったらね、ラップじゃないですか！
After all, when you think of Nqrse-san, it's gotta be rap, right?
で、この曲にラップがあるのかどうなのかっていうのは、まあこの後歌いますから、楽しみに待っていてほしいです。
As for whether there's rap in this song or not, I'm going to sing it now, so please look forward to finding out!
えー、MVに関してはですね、普段ちょっとやったことない動きをね、ディレクターさんに「こう動いてほしい」とか言われながら思考錯誤して頑張ってやって、ちょっと違和感もあるかもしれないけど頑張ったトワが見れるスタイリッシュなMVに仕上がりました。
As for the MV, I tried doing movements I don't usually do while working with the director through trial and error. It might feel a bit unusual, but it turned out to be a stylish MV where you can see how hard I worked.
なので、えー、この後のプレミア公開は楽しみにしておいてくれればなと思います。
So I hope you'll look forward to the premiere after this.
そしてね、この後、えー、なるせさんが書き下ろしてくださった「chewy chewy」を歌いたいと思いますので、
And next, I'm going to sing "chewy chewy" written by Nqrse-san...
ぜひ、えー...ちょっと待って、ここで落ち着かないとね。ぜひ、えー、聴いてもらえればと思います。では、「chewy chewy」。
...so please... wait a sec, I need to calm down first. I really hope you enjoy listening to it. Now then, "chewy chewy".
Shoot out like a boy 綺麗なもののボーイ
Shoot out like a boy, beautiful boy
Mimicry の coast to coast, coast to coast, bus to high
Mimicry, coast to coast, coast to coast, bus to high
からの girl 誰がフィクションの girl
And then girl, who is the fictional girl?
針を落として Do or die いざ Shall we go!
Drop the needle, do or die, now then, shall we go!
待たせ過ぎた？ 頂戴 しばってよ
Kept you waiting too long? Give it to me, tie me down
モノクロの劇場 好きなの？って
"Do you like monochrome theaters?" you ask
黒焦げた友情劇だって
Even a charred friendship drama
DemoのPage ヌメるGame
A demo page, a slimy game
どのハートも時計仕掛け
Every heart is clockwork
任された動機になって
Becoming an entrusted motive,
自由数はもう消し去っていいよ
it's fine to erase degrees of freedom now.
甘えを包む幻想や
The illusions wrapping up dependence,
触れられるのに掴めない
touchable, yet ungraspable,
水のように透き通るためらい
hesitation transparent as water,
どんな幸せの理論に冷め冷め
disillusioned by any theory of happiness.
忘れかけたもう
Already nearly forgotten,
忘れてきた知る由無き闇
the unknowable darkness left behind,
頭に響く警鐘
an alarm ringing in my head,
迷いもなく 振り向かない
without hesitation, I won't look back.
Manic, manic, mommy issue, wow!
Chewy chewy
くだらない いつだって
How pointless, every single time,
惑わせる 象徴
a perplexing symbol.
風に吹かれ 目に浮かぶ Fade out
Blown by the wind, fading out before my eyes,
くだらんね 焦がれたって 虚しいね
how silly, yearning is so empty.
火を灯せ ろくでなし 刺し違えて
Light a fire, you good-for-nothing, cross blades,
疑って お好きなの
doubt away, just as you like.
Catch me, sugar baby
Chewy Chew, Chewy Chew
モグモグモグ Chewy Chew, Chewy Chew
Mogu mogu mogu Chewy Chew, Chewy Chew
手を合わせる 何度も
Clasping hands together, time and again,
絡まった迷路
in an entangled maze.
騙されたまま居たいわ
I want to stay deceived,
退屈なの 浅い会話
shallow conversations are just boring.
傷は癒えぬまま居たいわ
I want to stay with my wounds unhealed,
消えちゃいたくて
just wanting to disappear.
まず足元見ないふり
First, pretending not to look at my feet,
帰る場所はどこだっけ？
where was my place to return to again?
今更で 傷一つねぇ
Too late now, without a single wound,
過去を抱いて 今を生きるの
embracing the past, I live in the present.
解かれぬままでも付かざるを得ない
Unsolved as it is, I have to go along with it,
騙し合いの恋でしょ
it's a love of mutual deceit, isn't it?
不気味な虫はBugger
Eerie insects are buggers,
この傷跡隠してリーダー
hiding these scars, leader.
大したことないと思うなら
If you think it's no big deal,
受け止めてよ
then accept it.
くだらない いつだって
How pointless, every single time,
惑わせる 象徴
a perplexing symbol.
風に吹かれ 目に浮かぶ Fade out
Blown by the wind, fading out before my eyes,
くだらんね 焦がれたって 虚しいね
how silly, yearning is so empty.
火を灯せ ろくでなし 刺し違えて
Light a fire, you good-for-nothing, cross blades,
疑って お好きなの
doubt away, just as you like.
Catch me, sugar baby
どうしたい？ でも思い立てず
What do you want to do? But unable to decide,
差し伸べないで 泣いて泣いて
don't reach out, crying and crying,
甘えちゃうわ
I'll end up depending on you.
さらばかつての自分よ
Farewell to my former self,
あなたを縛る時代よ
to the era that binds you.
もう Don't care 超 Don't care
Don't care anymore, super don't care,
この Journey away
on this journey away.
くだらない いつだって
How pointless, every single time,
惑わせる 象徴
a perplexing symbol.
風に吹かれ 目に浮かぶ Fade out
Blown by the wind, fading out before my eyes,
くだらんね 焦がれたって 虚しいね
how silly, yearning is so empty.
火を灯せ ろくでなし 刺し違えて
Light a fire, you good-for-nothing, cross blades,
疑って お好きなの
doubt away, just as you like.
Catch me, sugar baby
Chewy Chew, Chewy Chew
モグモグモグ Chewy Chew, Chewy Chew
Mogu mogu mogu Chewy Chew, Chewy Chew
手を合わせる 何度も
Clasping hands together, time and again,
絡まった迷路
in an entangled maze.
この道はどこへ続いているのだろう？
Where does this road lead?
目の前に
Before my eyes...
無数に
...countless...
別れた
...diverging...
可能性が広がっている。
...possibilities spread out.
ワタシは、私であるために
In order to be myself,
自分を縛る言葉は捨てて、広かっていくのは
I cast aside the words that bind me, and what spreads open...
私だけの、まだ知らない光。
...is a light of my own that I have yet to know.
10.29 ARIAKE ARENA
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live SHINier
進め。輝き溢れる、光の先へ。
Press on. Beyond the overflowing, brilliant light.
はい
Yes...
皆さん！
Everyone!
なんと！
Guess what!
えー、常闇トワのセカンドソロライブが...
Um, Tokoyami Towa's second solo live...
決定しましたー！
...has been confirmed!
イエーイ！
Yay!
おらー！来たぞー！
Hell yeah! Here it comes!
ついに公開されたー！
It's finally been announced!
よかったー！
I'm so glad!
ここまで色々あったんですけども、
So much has happened to get here,
まだここが始まりなんですけど、
and this is still just the beginning,
頑張りますからね！
but I'm going to work super hard!
どうですか？びっくりしました？
How was that? Were you surprised?
ありがとう！ありがとう！ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you so much!
泣きそう...わかる？
I feel like crying... Can you tell?
ちょっと泣きそうなの分かりますわ。
I can really tell I'm on the verge of tears.
一緒。
Same here.
でも取っておきましょう、それは。
But let's save those tears for later.
皆さん、今じゃないわ。取っとこう、本番までに。
Everyone, not now. Let's save them for the actual show.
えー、ということで、
So, with that said...
今回のライブタイトルは『Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live SHINier』！
...the title for this concert is "Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live SHINier"!
SHINierです
It's "SHINier".
えー、こちらなんですが、さっき発表したアルバムのね、タイトル「SHIN」に繋がってるんですよね。
Well, as for this name, it connects to the album title "SHIN" that we just announced.
このね、アルバムなんですけれども、色々な「SHIN」が入ってるアルバムとなってまして、
This album contains various kinds of "SHIN",
その「SHIN」に沿って今回のライブタイトルも「SHINier」という風につけさせていただきました。
and following that "SHIN", we named the title for this live concert "SHINier".
1stライブの「Scream」よりももっと輝いてかっこいい
It will be even brighter and cooler than my 1st Live, "Scream",
無限大の可能性を皆さんにお届けするので、ぜひ見に来てくれればなと思います。
and I will deliver infinite possibilities to you all, so I hope you'll come watch it.
はい。そしてキービジュアル見てみましょう！
Alright! And let me show you the key visual!
はい、どうですか？こちらね、アルバムのジャケット写真書いていただいた花沢さんにキービジュアルも一緒に描いていただきました！
How is it? For this, Hanazawa-san, who drew the cover for the album, drew the key visual for us too!
めっちゃかっこいいよね！
It's super cool, isn't it?
さっきのちょっと黒い暗い感じだったんだけど、こっちはね、光が見えるような感じで、
The previous one had a dark, black feeling, but for this one, you can see light,
進んでいくような前にいけるような明るさを演出してもらいましたね。
giving it a bright atmosphere that feels like moving forward.
すごいもうクールでかっこいい！けど、みたいな感じを出せればと思っております。
It's super cool and handsome! I hope to bring out that kind of vibe.
衣装もね、お気に入りです。当日楽しみです！
I really like the outfit, too. I'm excited for the day!
そして、今回のハッシュタグはライブ・アルバムどちらも共通で、ハッシュタグ「#常山...」
And for this time's hashtag, it's the same for both the live and album: "#Tokoyama..."
常山だって！トコヤミ！自分の名前噛むって凄くない？
Did I say Tokoyama?! Tokoyami! Isn't it crazy to stumble on my own name?
今なんかスタッフさんにめっちゃ見られて笑われてんだけど。恥ずかしいんだけど！
The staff members are staring at me and laughing so much right now. I'm so embarrassed!
#常闇トワ1st...セカンドです。
#TokoyamiTowa1st... 2nd.
もう帰りたい！ねえ、笑いすぎだから！
I want to go home! Hey, you're laughing too much!
じゃあ今日から改名して「常山」になります。よろしくお願いします。
Okay, from today I'll change my name to "Tokoyama". Nice to meet you.
皆さんいっぱいポストしてくれればなと思います！
I hope everyone posts a lot with it!
はい！そして皆さんお待ちかね、チケット情報です！
Yes! And next, the ticket information everyone's been waiting for!
本当に耳赤くなるんだけど。会場はなんと...
My ears are seriously turning red. The venue is...
有明アリーナです！はい！
Ariake Arena! Yes!
前回よりもね、もうー、すごいな、何倍？3倍？2.5倍？くらいね、
Compared to last time, wow, how many times bigger? 3 times? 2.5 times?
会場も広くなって、
The venue got so much bigger,
前回あんなに緊張して最初震えてたのに、
and last time I was so nervous that I was trembling at first,
大丈夫かなっていう心配で...
so I'm worried if I'll be okay...
全然実感湧かなかったんですけど、今この配信してちょっと実感が湧いてきて、プルプルしてきました。ドキドキしてます。でも頑張ります！
I didn't feel it at all before, but streaming right now makes it feel real, and I'm trembling. I'm nervous, but I'll do my best!
チケットはSS席、S席、A席、B席の4種類です。
There are 4 ticket tiers: SS, S, A, and B seats.
こちらのね、SS席が気になってると思うんですけれども、
You might be curious about the SS seats,
SS席と言うのは「SHINier Supporter」の略で、SHINierはトワのことで、そのサポーターは皆様のことなんですよね！
"SS seat" stands for "SHINier Supporter". "SHINier" means Towa, and the supporters are all of you!
そしてね、SS席には特典でブレスレットライトが付いてきます！
And SS seats come with a bonus bracelet light!
ちょっとお高いかもしれないんですけども、この席とかブレスレットライトが付いてくる点を考えると、
It might be a bit pricey, but considering the seating location and the bracelet light,
もう目の前で爆音で聴いて欲しいなっていう感じなんですけれどもね。
I really want you to hear the loud sound right in front of you.
このブレスレットライト、すごい作りたかったものなので、作れて本当に嬉しいです！
I really wanted to make this bracelet light, so I'm so happy we could make it!
ライブロゴやタイトルが入っている特別仕様で、紫色のかんごうがマグネットになっていて、付け外しができるようになっております。
It's a special edition with the live logo and title on it. The purple fastener is magnetic, making it detachable.
点灯カラーは白色になっておりまして、
The light color is white,
SS席のサポーターの皆様はこれで会場全体をキービジュアルみたいに光り輝かせていただければなと思います！
so I hope all the SS seat supporters can use it to light up the whole venue like the key visual!
すっごいいっぱいあるからさ、頑張ってね今。
There are so many things to announce, so I'm trying my best right now.
じゃあね、気になる各座席のエリアマップを見てみましょう！どんなもんじゃいということで、はい！
Now, let's take a look at the seating area map you're curious about! Let's see what it's like... Here!
そうなんです！SS席はなんとステージのど真ん中にあります！
That's right! The SS seats are right in front of the center of the stage!
で、その周りをS席、A席、B席という風に周りを囲んでいる形ですね。
And surrounding them are the S, A, and B seats.
現地チケットはこの後21時から1次抽選の申し込みが始まるので、みんなぜひ応募してください！
First-round lottery applications for venue tickets start at 21:00 today, so please apply!
海外の皆様も買えますのでよろしくお願いします！OVERSEAS BRO, SIS, みんな, Let's buy, let's go, let's go!
Overseas fans can buy them too! Overseas bro, sis, everyone, let's buy, let's go, let's go!
ま、でも現地に行けないよって人も大丈夫！配信チケットもあります！
Well, even if you can't come in person, don't worry! Streaming tickets are also available!
こちらもね、21時から発売開始なので、特設サイトをチェックしてみてください！
These also go on sale starting at 21:00, so please check out the special website!
概要欄にも更新してくれてると思うんですけども、リンクがありますので、
There should be a link in the description box as well,
あるけど、「常闇トワ 2nd Live」で検索しても
but even if you search for "Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live",
サイトで出てくるので、ブックマークしておくといいかもしれません。ちょっと出るか検索してみて、ちょっと心配だから。
it'll pop up on search engines, so bookmarking it might be good. Please search to see if it shows up, because I'm a bit worried.
配信でも現地でも、どちらもかっこいい、みんなが喜んでくれるようなパフォーマンスを頑張ってしたいと思いますので...
Whether on stream or at the venue, I'll do my best to deliver a cool performance that will make everyone happy, so...
頑張って走り抜けたいと思います！
I'll do my best to run all the way through to the end!
はい そしてここまではあっという間だったんですが 今回のライブ情報はここまでになります！
Time has flown by, but that's all for today's live concert info!
あれ？なんかライブに必要なものが足りなくない？って思ったそこの眷属！
"Wait, aren't we missing something essential for the live show?" To all the Kenzoku who thought that!
ちょっとカメラが大変だったんで あの あまり動かないようにしますけども
The camera work was pretty hectic, so I'll try not to move around too much.
ライブグッズは現在準備中になります！
The live concert merchandise is currently in preparation!
またね 別の日にね ライブグッズを発表する枠も取りたいと思いますから お楽しみに待っていてください
On another day, I'll schedule a stream to unveil the merch, so please look forward to it!
貯金タイムだから！いい？皆さん 貯金タイム！
This is saving time! Got it, everyone? Saving time!
と思いきや！ここまでがライブの告知 で 貯金タイムって言ったんだけど ここからは貯金しないでほしいタイムです！
Or so you thought! That was the concert announcement. I said it's saving time, but from here on out, it's time to spend!
常闇トワ誕生日記念2025のグッズ発売告知となりまーす！見てください こちら！
This is the announcement for Tokoyami Towa Birthday Celebration 2025 merch! Take a look at this!
イエーイ！rurudoマミーにイラスト描いてもらっちゃいました！マミーありがとー！かわいいよね！
Yay! rurudo-mommy drew this illustration for me! Thank you, Mommy! Isn't it cute?
はい 詳細をね みんなで見ていこうと思います！こちら！
Alright, let's check out the details together! Here!
じゃじゃーん！そう これマミーに描いてもらった ゴシックな部屋の撮影のトワちゃん！
Tada! Yes, this is Towa-chan taking photos in a gothic room, drawn by Mommy!
で ちょっと rurudoマミーの若干フェチがどこかに詰まってるんで どこか当ててくださいね！
And rurudo-mommy's slight fetishes are packed in here somewhere, so try to guess where!
はい そしてこちら！ビッグタオル！
Alright, next is this! Big Towel!
Mr.Lime先生に描いていただきました！Lime先生いつもありがとう！このね 配信のサムネも描いてくれました！ありがとう いつも！昔からずっと描いてくださっている先生です！
Illustrated by Mr.Lime-sensei! Thank you as always, Lime-sensei! He also drew the thumbnail for this stream! Thanks always! He's been drawing for me for a long time!
はい こちらもビッグサイズのタオル ぜひ使ってくれればなと思います！
Yes, this is also a big-sized towel, so I hope you'll use it!
続いてはこちら！ポン！トワ様とお出かけぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
Moving on to this! Bam! Towa-sama Going Out Plushie Keychain!
これはですね やっぱトワちゃんね 結構毎月「トワ旅」っていうのでみんながトワのぬいぐるみと一緒に旅行してくれて それを行った気持ちになる配信があるんですけども
So, every month we have "Towa Travel", where everyone travels around with a Towa plushie and streams about it, making us feel like we went along.
やっぱ私服でね ちょっと デートというか デートとして行ってもいいっていう意味を込めて 私服のミニチュアサイズというか 持ち運びできるようなお出かけぬいぐるみキーホルダーを作らせていただきましたので
So in her casual outfit, meant for like a date... you can take her out on dates! I made a portable mini plushie keychain in her casual outfit!
また買って届いたら いっぱい投稿してくれればなと思います！
So once you buy it and it arrives, I hope you'll post lots of photos!
はい そしてこちら！眷属メタルキーホルダー！
Alright, and next is this! Kenzoku Metal Keychain!
可愛い Bibi と あとはトワ やっぱり歌ももちろん大好きなんですけども ゲームもやっぱりすごい好きなので
Cute Bibi, and Towa... of course I love singing, but I also really love gaming...
そのイメージをこちらに詰め込んでいただけました！可愛いでしょ キーホルダー！
So those themes are packed into this! Cute keychain, right?
最近トワね いろんなところにキーホルダーをジャラジャラつけるのにはまってるんで 作ってみました！よろしくお願いします！
Lately Towa has been into jingling lots of keychains everywhere, so I made this! Please check it out!
フルセットの購入特典もございますので見てみましょう！
There's also a full-set purchase bonus, so let's check it out!
はい！rurudoマミーのちょっとペロッみたいな表情差分があるトワちゃんの 箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきまーす！
Yes! A Polaroid-style bromide card with a foil-stamped printed signature of Towa-chan with a cute tongue-out expression variant by rurudo-mommy is included!
はい フルセット買ってみるとついてくるんだよ これが！
Yes, if you buy the full set, you get this!
でもね！そしてね！しかもね！なんと もう一個ついてきちゃうの！こちら！
But wait! And also! What's more! You actually get one more item! Here!
戻ってね あ これだった ごめん あれ これか？フルセットはこれ！
Going back... Ah, it was this, sorry. Wait, this one? Here's the full set!
はい これ！1 2 3 4 5 これね！これがついてきて で これ！これがついてくる！次！
Yes, this! 1, 2, 3, 4, 5... this! You get this, and this! Next!
これこれこれこれ！もう大盤振る舞いしながら！これがついてきます！カードがついてきますよ！hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAMEで使用できるカードが1枚ついてきます！
This, this, this, this! We're being super generous! This comes with it! A card is included! 1 playable card for the hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME!
カードはね ホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで購入された方のみ対象となっております
Note that this card bonus is only for purchases made on the Hololive Production Official Shop.
特典につくのは 推しアピールできるキーカード 推しホロメンカードです！
The bonus item is an Oshi Holomen card, a key card to show off your favorite!
カードの詳細や遊び方についてはホームページで確認してねい！
Please check the official website for details on the card and how to play!
ということで以上 常闇トワ誕生日記念グッズの情報でした！
And that wraps up the announcement for Tokoyami Towa's Birthday Commemorative Merch!
みんな買ってね！これで素敵なMV作るんだから！買ってくれないといいの作れないから！よろしくね！
Everyone, please buy it! I'm going to make a great MV with this! If you don't buy it, I can't make a good one! Thank you!
はい そして！そして！先ほどお伝えした 2ndアルバム『SHIN』がホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップでの販売が先行して開始しております！
And also! As mentioned earlier, pre-orders for my 2nd album "SHIN" have already started early on the Hololive Production Official Shop!
はい 多分配信画面の下に出てきた購入ボタンから販売ページに飛べるようになっていると思うんですけども 皆さん 押せるようになりました？
Yes, you can probably jump to the store page using the buy button below the stream window, but is everyone able to click it now?
もしなかったらね 更新でおねがいいたします 更新してください
Ah, if it's not showing up, please refresh the page. Please hit refresh.
購入ボタンをクリックする前に注意事項なんですが 2ndアルバムとそれ以外のものを同じカートで購入していただいた場合に 発売日の10月8日までに発送が行われない可能性があるので気を付けてください！
Before clicking buy, here's an important note: if you purchase the 2nd album together with other items in the same cart, it might not be shipped by the October 8th release date, so please be careful!
2ndアルバム単体での購入なら大丈夫です！
If you purchase the 2nd album by itself, you'll be fine!
ありがとう！買った ありがとう ありがとうね！ありがとう！
Thank you! You bought it? Thank you! Thank you so much! Thank you!
は、このあと9時からになりますからね。
...will be available starting from 9:00, okay?
ありがとうございます！買ってくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much! Thank you for buying!
はい、そしてもうあと少し、このあと8時50分、Chewy ChewyのMVプレミア公開がありまして、
Yes, and coming up shortly, at 8:50, the music video for "Chewy Chewy" will premiere,
えー、9時からライブチケットの発売がございます！
and ticket sales for the concert will open at 9:00!
ということで、今日は1時間枠じゃなくてちょっと短いんですけれど、
So, today's stream was a bit shorter than a full hour,
こんな感じで、また後日配信すると思うので、
but I'll be streaming again another day,
ぜひまた遊びに来てください！
so please come watch again!
はい！では皆さん！
All right, everyone!
このあとChewy Chewy、ここにいたらすぐ消えるんで、かっこいいMV行けるんで、ここに待機して、しばし待たれよ！
"Chewy Chewy" is up next! If you stay here, you can jump straight to the cool MV, so stay put and wait just a moment!
ということで、今日はありがとー！いっぱいポストしてねー！
So, thank you for today! Post lots of tweets, okay?
駆け足になっちゃった、またねー！
It was super rushed! See you later!